theskimm.com 2019-11-15

# Privacy Notice

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Last Revised: April, 2019

theSkimm, Inc. ("theSkimm" "we" or "us") is the owner and operator of (i) the Site and the App (as such terms are defined in the Terms of Service for the Site and App); and (ii)the Platform (as defined in the Terms of Use for the Platform) and the provider of the Services. theSkimm respects your privacy, and we created this privacy policy (the "Policy") to explain how we collect, use and disclose your information when you access the Site, the App, and the Platform and use the Services. The Policy is only applicable to our Site, the App, the Platform, and our Services and not to any other website, service or online platform. Capitalized terms that are not defined in this Policy have the meaning given them in our Terms of Service or Terms of Use, as applicable. BY ACCESSING THE SITE, THE APP, THE PLATFORM, UTILIZING ANY OF THE SERVICES AND/OR REGISTERING WITH US, YOU SIGNIFY THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTOOD AND AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS POLICY, INCLUDING OUR TERMS OF SERVICE AND/OR TERMS OF USE, AS APPLICABLE, WHICH ARE INCORPORATED HEREIN BY REFERENCE.

 **Types of Information Collected**

Personal Information

theSkimm may ask you for some or all of the following types of information which may be identifiable to you when you register for our App, the Platform, or other Services, access various content or features, or directly contact the site: (i) contact information, such as your email address and name; (ii) your age; and (iii) information for the purpose of authenticating yourself or your account if we have reason to believe, in our sole discretion, that you may be violating site policies or for any other reason we deem necessary (collectively "Personal Information"). We do not collect any Personal Information from you when you use the Site, App, Platform or Services unless you provide it voluntarily. You are responsible for ensuring the accuracy of all Personal Information you submit to theSkimm.  
We also collect and store the Personal Information you voluntarily submit to us through registering with us or uploading or posting User Content through the Site, the App or Services. If you are signed into your Tumblr, Twitter or Facebook account and you "like" or "comment" on theSkimm Content (such as the articles found on our blog) or other User Content, your Tumblr, Twitter or Facebook username will be displayed and so available to the public. You agree that your username, likes, feedback, and any associated comments may become public information; we therefore urge you to exercise caution when deciding to disclose any Personal Information on the Site, the App or through the Services.

In addition, if you choose to purchase or subscribe to the App or a feature or Services of theSkimm that requires a Fee, you will be required to provide us with your billing information, including, without limitation, bank account numbers, credit card or debit card numbers, account details, ACH information, and similar data (collectively, "Billing Information").

Non-Personal Information

theSkimm may collect additional information that you provide to theSkimm voluntarily through the Platform, such as household income range, personal interests, and any of your product or service preferences (“Other Information”).

Cookies and Other Technologies. We may utilize cookies and other technologies, such as, web beacons (also known as "clear gifs" and "pixel tags") to recognize you, customize your experience, and serve advertisements. Cookies are very small files placed on your computer, and they allow us to count the number of visitors to theSkimm and distinguish repeat visitors from new visitors. They also allow us to save User preferences and track User trends. We may also enable advertisers and ad servers to promote third party products and/or services by placing advertisements on theSkimm. These advertisers and ad servers may use cookies and/or web beacons to monitor information related to served advertisements. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Policy covers the use of cookies by theSkimm and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. If you do not want us to deploy cookies in your browser, you can opt out by setting your browser to reject cookies or to notify you when a website tries to put a cookie in your browser software. If you choose to disable cookies in your browser, you can still use the Site, the App, the Platform, and the Services, although your ability to use some of the features may be affected.

Information Collected Automatically. We automatically receive and collect information such as your IP address, the URLs of websites you arrive at theSkimm from or leave theSkimm to go to, your type of browser and language, access times, the content of any undeleted cookies that your browser previously accepted from us, your operating system, your mobile provider, your mobile device, and your ISP. We may use such information to better understand how theSkimm visitors use the Site, the App, and the Platform, to analyze trends, administer the website, prevent fraud, and gather broad demographic information.

Our Use of Your Information

Our primary purpose in collecting information, both Personal Information and any other information, is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. You agree that we may use your information to: provide the Services and customer support you request; troubleshoot problems and prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities; customize, measure and improve our Site, the App, the Platform, our Services, content and advertising; tell you about and administer our Site, App, Platform, or Services, targeted marketing, service updates, contests, sweepstakes, rewards, and promotional offers based on your communication preferences; monitor and enforce our Terms of Service; communicate with Users about third-party products and/or services you may be interested in; verify your eligibility to use the Site, the App, or the Platform.

Our Disclosure of Your Information

theSkimm is committed to maintaining your trust and we want you to understand when and with whom we may share information collected about you. We may disclose Personal Information, Billing Information and Non-Personal Information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a listing or other content violates the rights of others, or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety. Such information will be disclosed in accordance with applicable laws and regulations.

We may also use and/or share your Personal Information, Billing Information and Non-Personal Information with, and you authorize us to use and/or share this information with:

\- Service providers under contract who help with our business operations. We employ these companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products and services to you.

\- We will share your Billing Information with a third party service provider as necessary to process your payments. The third party service provider stores your Billing Information; we do not store this information. Storage by the third party service provider of your Billing Information is subject to the privacy policies and practices of the third party service provider and is not subject to the terms of this privacy policy. By providing your Billing Information, you acknowledge and agree to use of such information by the third party service provider for purposes of processing your payment to us.

\- Certain of theSkimm's program participants under confidentiality agreement, as we in our sole discretion believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity.

\- Our affiliates and promotional partners, so they can offer you special products, services, discounts, tickets, and other items or services. Likewise, we may receive information from such affiliates and promotional partners to offer our Users special items or services.

\- We may combine your information with information we collect from other companies and use it to improve and personalize our services, content and advertising.

\- We may sell or rent your information to third parties for marketing purposes without your explicit consent.

\- In an ongoing effort to better understand our Users, we may analyze certain Non-Personal Information in anonymized and aggregate form in order to operate, maintain, manage, and improve the Site, the App, the Platform, the Services and/or such products and services. This aggregate information does not identify you personally. We may share and/or license this aggregate data to our affiliates, agents, business and promotional partners and other third parties. We may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe the Services and these products and services to current and prospective business partners and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.

\- We may share some or all of your Information with any of our parent companies, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under common control with us.

\- As we develop our businesses, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, sale of assets, dissolution, or similar event, the Information may be part of the transferred assets.

If you do not wish to receive marketing communications from us or participate in our ad-customization programs, simply indicate your preference or by following the directions provided with the communication or advertisement.

Microsoft Skype Bot

Our Microsoft Skype Bot is enabled by Microsoft Bot Framework. The Microsoft Bot Framework is a set of web-services that enable intelligent services and connections using conversation channels you authorize. As a service provider, Microsoft will transmit content you provide to our bot/service in order to enable the service. For more information about Microsoft privacy policies please see their privacy statement here: http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkId=521839. In addition, your interactions with this bot/service are also subject to the conversational channel's applicable terms of use, privacy and data collection policies. To report abuse when using a bot that uses the Microsoft Bot Framework to Microsoft, please visit the Microsoft Bot Framework website at https://www.botframework.com and use the “Report Abuse” link in the menu to contact Microsoft.

No Spam or Spyware

We do not tolerate spam. Spamming is explicitly prohibited it by our Terms of Service. If you would like to report an incident of spamming or other unauthorized communications from other Users or Instructors, please contact us at founders@theSkimm.com. We maintain the right to investigate such incidents and take suitable action.

Account Protection

We take commercially reasonable steps to protect your information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. Nevertheless, no transmission over the Internet and no data storage method can be guaranteed to be safe 100% of the time. theSkimm cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to theSkimm or guarantee that your end user data stored on the App, the Platform, or the Services may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our industry standard physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. In particular, e-mail sent to us may not be secure, and you should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us via e-mail.

The Site, the App, and the Platform are hosted on servers in the United States. Accordingly, if you are located outside of the United States, any information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. By providing us with any information, you consent to its transfer and storage in the United States.

Email Communications

We may use your email to deliver theSkimm's daily newsletter, as well as for other promotional (e.g., new product offerings, special offers by us or other third parties) purposes. Email messages we send you may contain code that enables our database to track your usage of the emails we send you, such usage includes whether the email was opened and what links (if any) were clicked. If you send an email to us, or fill out our "Feedback" form, we will collect your email address and the full content of your email, including attached files, and other information you provide.

You may indicate your preference to opt out of receiving promotional communications by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the promotional email you receive or by contacting us directly at founders@theSkimm.com. You acknowledge that it may take up to 10 days for us to process an opt-out request. Please note, however, that you cannot opt out of receiving transactional e-mails related to your account with us.

Third Parties

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Policy, this document addresses only the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. If you disclose your information to others Users or Instructors on the Platform, our Site or on other sites throughout the internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. We do not control the privacy policies of third parties, and you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties where applicable. We are not responsible for any information we do not collect. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your Personal Information or Other Information to others.

NOTE THAT INSTRUCTORS ARE THIRD PARTIES AND NOT EMPLOYEES OF THESKIMM, AND AS SUCH, theSkimm is not in control of any information that you voluntarily provide to Instructors, and any such provision of information to Instructors will be governed by any agreements entered into by you with such Instructor.

Children

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important to us. For that reason, theSkimm does not knowingly collect or solicit Personal Information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are under 13, please do not give us any Personal Information. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children's Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children never to provide Personal Information through the Site or the App without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Information to us, please contact us, and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases.

California Residents

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits residents of the State of California to request certain information regarding our disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please email us at founders@theSkimm.com or write us at: theSkimm, Inc., Attn: Legal - California Privacy Compliance, 50 West 23rd Street, Suite 5B, New York, New York, 10010.

In addition, theSkimm does not monitor, recognize, or honor any opt-out or do not track mechanisms, including general web browser "Do Not Track" settings and/or signals.

Changes to this Policy

We reserve the right, at any time, to add to, change, update, or modify this Policy. Any such changes to this Policy will be posted here on our Site so we urge to please visit this page frequently. In all cases, use of information we collect is subject to the Policy in effect at the time such information is collected. Please refer back to this Privacy Policy on a regular basis.

How to Contact Us

If you wish to request a copy of or make updates to your personal information collected by theSkimm, please contact us at privacy@theskimm.com.
